One.
Một.
And look! The one who's got the ball, he plays for us.
Và nhìn kìa! Người có bóng, cậu ấy chơi cho đội mình.
Oh yes, he looks very dirty.
Ồ đúng rồi, cậu ấy trông rất bẩn.
Oh Mum, listen, his name's Tom.
Ôi Mẹ ơi, nghe này, cậu ấy tên Tom.
So he's the dirty one?
Vậy cậu ấy là người bẩn á?
Yes Mum.
Vâng Mẹ.
Two.
Hai.
And there's Tom's sister, Vicki.
Và đó là chị gái của Tom, Vicki.
Where dear?
Ở đâu con?
There, look, sitting on the grass with her doll.
Đó, nhìn kìa, đang ngồi trên cỏ với con búp bê.
Oh, now she looks bored, very bored. So she doesn't play football then?
Ồ, bây giờ bạn ấy trông chán, rất chán. Vậy bạn ấy không chơi bóng đá à?
No Mum.
Không Mẹ.
Three.
Ba.
And that's Tom's dad, there.
Và đó là bố của Tom, ở đó.
Where?
Ở đâu?
He's taking a picture of Tom.
Bác ấy đang chụp ảnh Tom.
Oh, you mean with the blue sweater?
Ồ, con nói người mặc áo len xanh dương á?
Yes. Well, he's Bill.
Đúng rồi. À, bác ấy là Bill.
That's nice.
Hay đấy.
Four.
Bốn.
Now look at that boy. He's standing there and he isn't playing.
Bây giờ nhìn cậu bé đó. Cậu ấy đứng đó và không chơi.
Well, he isn't very happy Mum.
À, cậu ấy không vui lắm Mẹ ạ.
But he's got his hands on his head.
Nhưng cậu ấy đặt hai tay lên đầu.
Yes. Well, his name's John.
Vâng. À, cậu ấy tên John.
I see.
Mẹ hiểu rồi.
Five.
Năm.
Now, who's that woman there? She looks very nice.
Bây giờ, ai là người phụ nữ ở đó? Cô ấy trông rất dễ thương.
She's showing some photos to her friend.
Cô ấy đang khoe mấy tấm ảnh cho bạn xem.
The one with the scarf you mean?
Con nói người đeo khăn quàng á?
Yes.
Đúng vậy.
Oh, she's John's Mum. Her name's Kim.
Ồ, cô ấy là mẹ của John. Cô ấy tên Kim.
Oh, now I'd like to talk to her.
Ồ, bây giờ mẹ muốn nói chuyện với cô ấy.
Oh Mum.
Ôi Mẹ.
Now listen to part one again.
Bây giờ hãy nghe lại phần một.
That is the end of part one.
Đó là phần kết thúc của phần một.